Guide to the Robert L. Eichelberger Papers, 1728-1998 (bulk 1942-1949)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Robert L. Eichelberger papers 1728-1998 (bulk 1942-1949)
Eichelberger, Robert L., 1886-1961
54 linear feet Extent: 29,056 items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.00376
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Online Items
Photographs from Siberia, 1918-1919, have been digitized and are available in Americans in the Land of Lenin - Duke Digital Collections
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Eichelberger Papers were donated to the Special Collections Library in several installments from 1955 to 1999.
Biographical Note
1886 March 9 Born Urbana, Ohio
1903-1905 Attended Ohio State University
1909 Graduated from the United States Military Academy at West Point
1913 Married Emma Gudger
1918-1920 Served in Siberia as Assistant Chief of Staff, Operations Division, and Chief Intelligence Officer with the American Expeditionary Forces
1920-1921 Served in Japan, China, and the Philippines in connection with military intelligence activities
1921-1924 Served in the Military Intelligence Division, War Department General Staff in Washington, D.C.
1925-1929 Student and instructor at the Command and General Staff School, Ft. Leavenworth, Kan.
1930 Graduated from Army War College in Washington, D.C.
1939-1940 Assumed command of the 30th Infantry, Presidio of San Francisco
1940-1942 Appointed Superintendent of the United States Military Academy, West Point, N.Y.
1942 Jan. Designated Commander of the Seventy-seventh Army Division, organized at Fort Jackson, S.C.
1942 Dec.-1943 Jan. Participated in the Buna and Sanananda, New Guinea campaigns
1943 Sept. Promoted to Brigadier General
1944 April Commanded task force which captured Hollandia, Dutch New Guinea
1944 June Commanded Biak Task Force which retook land from the Japanese
1944 Sept. Became commanding general, Eighth Army
1945 Jan-Aug. Eighth Army under Eichelberger's command fought on every occupied island of the Philippine Archipelago
1945 Aug 30 Participated in the occupation of Japan by landing at Atsugi Air Field in Honshu with the Eighth Army and a detachment from the 11th Airborne Division
1946 Jan. 1 Assumed control of all ground occupation troops in Japan
1948 Dec. 31 Retired from the Army
1949 Eichelberger's memoir, Our Bloody Jungle Road to Tokyo, was serialized in the Saturday Evening Post
1954 Promoted to the rank of four star general by an Act of Congress
1961 Sept. 26 Died, buried in Arlington National Cemetery
Eichelberger received the following medals and honors: Distinguished Service Cross with one oak leaf cluster, Distinguished Service Medal with three clusters, Combat Infantry Badge, Distinguished Service Medal (Navy), Silver Star with two clusters, Legion of Merit, Bronze Star Medal, the Presidential Unit Citation with one cluster, Honorary Knight Commander of the Military Division of the Most Excellent Order of the British Empire, Grand Officer of the Order of Orange Nassau with swords (Holland), Grand Officer of the Legion of Honor (France), Grand Officer of the Order of the Crown of Belgium, the Croix de Guerre with palm (Belgium), and Order of ABDON Calderon First Class (Ecuador). He was granted the Distinguished Service Star, the Liberation Medal, and the Legion of Honor by the Republic of the Philippines. He also received the decoration, Grand Officer of the Military Order of Italy.
Collection Overview
The Eichelberger Papers span the period 1728 to 1998, with the bulk of the collection dating between 1942 and 1949. The papers contain diaries, correspondence, military papers, writings and speeches, pictures, scrapbooks, printed material, clippings, memorabilia, and audiovisual material chiefly relating to Eichelberger's military career. Prominently highlighted is his participation as a member of the American Expeditionary Forces in Siberia (1918-1920); the military campaigns he led in New Guinea and the Philippines during World War II (1942-1945); and the post-war period when he commanded all ground occupation troops in Japan (1945-1948). Additionally, there are several photographs of Winston Churchill, who came to Fort Jackson, S.C. in 1942, to view the 77th Army Division commanded by Eichelberger. There are also several photographs of Eleanor Roosevelt, when she came to Australia in 1943 to visit the troops, and several of Douglas MacArthur. The bulk of the personal correspondence (1942-1945) was written by Eichelberger to his wife, Emma Gudger Eichelberger, in which he described the fighting in the Pacific as well as the difficulties of jungle life. In dictations after the war, Eichelberger reflected upon his military career and various people, including Generals Douglas MacArthur, George C. Marshall, Dwight D. Eisenhower, and Robert C. Richardson.
Eichelberger's military career is represented in all series throughout the collection. In particular, the dictations Eichelberger made after the war are located in the Writings and Speeches Series. The extensive Pictures Series documents the events of his career during 1918 to 1920, and during World War II and the post-war period. Eichelberger's memoir, Our Bloody Jungle Road to Tokyo, serialized in the Saturday Evening Post in 1949, is located in the Oversize Printed Material Series.
Related materials include a microfilm (2 reels) of the 1949 Ph.D. dissertation written at Syracuse University by Duke Professor Ralph Braibanti, The Occupation of Japan, which contains information about Eichelberger while he was commander of the occupation troops in Japan after World War II. This microfilm is located in Perkins Library Microforms Department. The Duke University Special Collections Library also has the papers of Eichelberger's father George M. Eichelberger, a lawyer from Urbana, Ohio. Another related collection is the Westall Family Papers. Mrs. James M. Westall (Virginia Cooper Westall), was Eichelberger's longtime secretary in Asheville, N.C. There are over a hundred letters of Eichelberger's and other related materials in this collection which document the Eichelbergers' business and social affairs from the 1950s until his death.
Other related works include a compilation of Eichelberger's letters to his wife entitled Dear Miss Em: General Eichelberger's War in the Pacific, 1942-1945, (Westpoint, Conn., 1972) edited by Jay Luvaas. Other works about Eichelberger include Forged by Fire: General Robert L. Eichelberger and the Pacific War (Columbia, S.C., 1987) by John F. Shortal, and "A 'Near Great' General: the Life and Career of Robert L. Eichelberger," a Duke University 1991 Ph.D. dissertation, by Paul Chwialkowski.
The addition (acc# 1999-0167) (83 reels; dated 1998) consists of negative microfilm reels of the Japan and America microfilm series, photographed from the Eichelberger Papers.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Eichelberger, Robert L.; Japan -- History -- Allied occupation, 1945-1952; North Carolina State Ports Authority; United States.--Army -- Officers; United States Military Academy -- Students; World War, 1939-1945 -- Campaigns; North Carolina -- Buncombe County -- Asheville; Microfilm
Contents of Collection
- Diaries, 1909-1961 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  Arranged in chronological order, with loose papers from individual volumes placed in folders immediately following that particular volume.
  - 1909-1916 (Box 1)
  - 1942
  - 1943
  - 1944, (2 volumes)
  - 1945-1946
  - 1947
  - 1940 Nov.-1947, (5 folders)
  - 1948, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - 1949, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1950, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1951, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1952, (2 volumes)
  - 1953 (Box 3)
  - 1954, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1955, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1956-1957, (2 volumes)
  - 1958, (1 volume, 1 folder)
  - 1959-1960, (2 volumes)
  - 1961 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1872-1962 (bulk 1942-1949)
  Contains handwritten notes and letters, typed letters, memoranda, and telegrams. Arranged in chronological order primarily by year and month. Correspondence between 1943 and 1949 has been categorized as either personal or official. Before 1943 and after 1949, the official and personal correspondence is filed together. At the time of processing, the papers were already organized in this manner. A few folders have been divided by correspondent or topic of correspondence.
  Condolences sent after Eichelberger's death are included at the end of the series. One envelope of alphabetized file slips compiled by Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library staff indexes letters in the Correspondence Series. The envelope is filed in the Information Folder in the Collection Inventory Drawer.
  - Personal and Official Subseries
    - 1872-1919 Sept., (6 folders) (Box 5)
    - 1919 Oct.-1942 Sept., (6 folders) (Box 6)
    - 1942 Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Personal Subseries
    - 1943 Jan.-May, (3 folders)
    - 1943 June-1944 June, (6 folders) (Box 8)
    - 1944 July-1945 Apr., (7 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1945 May-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 10)
    - 1946-1947, (8 folders) (Box 11)
    - 1948 Jan-Oct., (14 folders) (Box 12)
    - 1948 Nov.-1949 Apr., (8 folders) (Box 13)
    - 1949 May-Aug., (5 folders) (Box 14)
    - 1949 Sept.-Dec., undated, (7 folders) (Box 15)
  - Official Subseries
    - 1943-1947, (7 folders) (Box 16)
    - 1948-1949, undated, (4 folders) (Box 17)
  - Personal and Official Subseries
    - 1950, (7 folders)
    - 1951-1953, (8 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1954, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1955, (2 folders)
    - 1956 Jan.-Aug., (2 folders)
    - 1956 Sept.-1958 Jan., (9 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1958 Feb.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1959, (7 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1960-1961 Apr., (8 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1961 May-1971 undated, (6 folders) (Box 24)
    - Algase, Gertrude, 1946-1950 Mar., (4 folders) (Box 25)
    - Asheville Chamber of Commerce Review Board, 1955-1958, (2 folders)
    - North Carolina State Ports Authority, 1959-1960, (2 folders)
  - Condolences Subseries
    - 1961 Sept. 26-Oct. 12, (9 folders) (Box 26)
    - 1961 Oct. 13-1962 Apr., undated, (6 folders) (Box 27)
- Military Papers, 1912-1960, undated (bulk 1942-1948)
  Subdivided into five subseries: Siberian Expedition, World War II, World War II: Japan, Japan: Occupation, and Miscellaneous. The sequence reflects the order in which these events occurred.
  - Siberian Expedition, 1917-1924, undated
    Includes maps, typed letters, handwritten notes, intelligence summaries, memoranda, reports, and leaflets. Arranged in chronological order, then alphabetically by topic where applicable.
    - 1917-1918, (4 folders) (Box 28)
    - 1918, Cole, Frank L., Notes on Siberian Expedition
    - 1918-1919
    - 1919, (5 folders) (Box 29)
    - 1919:
      - Land Defense of Vladivostok, Siberia, Aug.
      - Packard, Laurence B., The Czecho-Slovaks in Russia: Aug. 1914-Feb. 1919
    - Phillip, Karl
    - Reports, 1919 Jan. 3-Feb. 7
    - 1919 Jan. 3-Oct. 10, Reports, (5 folders) (Box 30)
    - 1919 Oct. 11-1920, Reports, (4 folders) (Box 31)
    - 1920 Jan.-1924, (2 folders)
    - 1920, summary, American and Allied Intervention
    - 1920, Trupp, Eugene, Leaflets from the History of the Civil War in Russia
    - 1921-1922
    - Miscellaneous, undated
  - World War II, 1942-1951, undated (bulk 1942-1945)
    Includes administrative and field orders, notes on various campaigns, maps, intelligence reports, military strategic studies, operations instructions, reports, letters, staff studies, statistics, and historical reports. Chiefly arranged in alphabetical order by topic, then chronologically. The Campaigns topic is further subdivided by name of individual campaigns.
    - Activation of the 77th Division, 1942 Jan-July (Box 32)
    - Administrative Orders, 1945 Jan.-June, (2 volumes)
    - Campaigns: (Box 33)
      - Biak, Schouten Islands, 1944, (4 folders)
      - Buna, New Guinea, 1942-1948, undated, (5 folders, 1 volume)
      - Hollandia, New Guinea, 1943-1944, (6 folders) (Box 34)
      - Leyte-Samar, P.I., 1944-1946, (5 folders) (Box 35)
      - Lingayen, P.I., 1944
      - Luzon, P.I., 1944, Nov.
      - Luzon, P.I., 1944-1945, (6 folders) (Box 36)
      - Luzon, P.I., 1945, (2 folders) (Box 37)
      - Maps, 1949
      - Mindanao, P.I., 1945, undated, (3 folders, 2 volumes)
      - Mindoro-Marindugue, P.I., 1945 (Box 38)
      - Nasugbu, P.I., 1944
      - Palawan, Zamboanga and Jolo, P.I., 1945, (6 folders, 1 volume)
      - Panay, Negros, and Cebu, P.I., 1945, undated, (4 folders)
      - Panay, Negros, and Cebu, P.I., 1945, (1 volume) (Box 39)
    - Field orders, 1944 Oct.-1945 June, (2 volumes) (Box 40)
    - Naval Intelligence report: Prominent Persons in Japan and Japanese Dominated Areas, 1945 Aug. (Box 41)
    - Office of Chief of Military History: Leyte: Return to the Philippines, undated, (2 volumes)
    - Office of Military History: The U.S. Army in World War II, The Approach to the Philippines, 1951 (Box 42)
    - Operations Instructions, 1944 Dec.-1945 Sept., (3 volumes) (Box 43)
    - Operations Instructions, 1945 July-Dec., (2 volumes) (Box 44)
    - Operations of the Intelligence Service in the Southwest Pacific Area, 1948 July
    - Pearl Harbor Investigative reports: (Box 45)
      - 1944
      - Report of Army Pearl Harbor Board, 1944, (2 volumes)
    - Report (Biennial): The Chief of Staff of the United States Army, 1943 July-1945 June (Box 46)
    - Report: The Supreme Commander to the Combined Chief of Staff, 1944 June-1945 May
    - Training Directives, 1944 Oct.-1945 Nov.
    - Miscellaneous, 1942-1945
  - World War II: Japan, 1944-1945.
    Contains information relating to the invasion of Japan, code name Operation Coronet. Includes numerous intelligence studies and reports about Japan, military proposals, and maps.
    - Operation Coronet (Invasion of Japan), 1944-1945 May, (4 volumes) (Box 47)
    - Operation Coronet (Invasion of Japan), 1945 May-1945, (1 folder, 4 volumes) (Box 48)
  - Japan: Occupation, 1945-1960, undated (bulk 1945-1948)
    Contains numerous studies regarding the economic, educational, social, and political restructuring of Japan during its occupation after World War II. Includes intelligence reports, monthly military summaries, correspondence between the Japanese government and the Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers (SCAP), war trial reports, monthly non-military summaries, Eighth Army reports, United States Army occupational reports, letters, and notes. Arranged in alphabetical order by type or title of material, then chronologically.
    - Administrative Orders, 1945-1946, (4 volumes) (Box 49)
    - Civil Intelligence Section: Occupational Trends: Japan and Korea, 1945 Dec.-1946 Apr., (2 folders)
    - Civil Intelligence Section: Occupational Trends: Japan and Korea, 1946 May-June (Box 50)
    - Civil Intelligence Section: Occupational Trends: Japan, Korea, Philippines, 1946 July
    - Economics, 1945-1949, undated, (3 folders)
    - Editors and Publishers Tour of Kobe, Japan, 1947 (Box 51)
    - Education, 1948 May-July, (1 folder, 2 volumes)
    - Eighth Army Field Orders, 1945
    - Eighth Army in Japan, 1945 Aug.-1946 May, undated
    - Far East War Trials: (Box 52)
      - 1945-1948, undated
      - Special Study of the Yokahama War Crimes Trials, 1945 Dec.-1947 Sept.
    - Food, 1948, undated
    - Memoranda to Imperial Japanese Government from SCAP (Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers), 1945 Sept.-Dec., (1 folder, 1 volume)
    - Memoranda to Imperial Japanese Government from SCAP (Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers), 1945 Nov. -1946 Jan., (2 folders, 1 volume) (Box 53)
    - Military Government Reports, 1945-1951, undated, (3 folders)
    - Monthly Military Summaries, 1946 July-1947 July, (1 folder) (Box 54)
    - Monthly Military Summaries in Korea 1946 March-July, (5 volumes)
    - Monthly Military Summaries in Korea, 1946 Aug.-Sept., (2 volumes) (Box 55)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1945 Sept.-Nov., (2 volumes)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1945 Dec.-1946 Feb., (3 volumes) (Box 56)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1946 March-June, (4 volumes) (Box 57)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1946 July-Nov., (5 volumes) (Box 58)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1946 Dec.-1947 July, (6 volumes) (Box 59)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1947 Aug.-Dec., (5 volumes) (Box 60)
    - Monthly Non-Military Summaries, 1948 Jan.-May, (5 volumes) (Box 61)
    - Occupation Plans, 1945 July-1949 May, undated, (1 volume, 4 folders) (Box 62)
    - Occupation Plans: Directives, 1945 Sept.-1948 Apr., undated, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Political Reorganization of Japan, 1947 Aug.-1949 Oct.
    - Public Health and Welfare Reports, 1945-1949
    - Report on Industrial Reparations, 1948 Feb., (2 folders)
    - Special Staff Study of the Repatriation of German Nationals from Japan, 1947 May, (2 folders)
    - Sugayomo Prison: A Special Study, 1945 Nov.-1947 Jan. (Box 64)
    - Two Years of Occupation by SCAP (Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers) and Far East Command, 1947 Aug.
    - Miscellaneous, 1945-1949, undated, (3 folders)
  - Miscellaneous, 1912-1960, undated (bulk 1946-1949).
    Contains various letters, reports, memoranda, newspaper articles, dictation, and notes. Arranged in alphabetical order by topic then chronologically.
    - Eisenhower's Inspection of Kobe Base, 1946 May 14 (Box 65)
    - Klein, Juluis, Brigadier General, 1949
    - Sorge Spy Reports, 1947 Dec.-1949 Feb.
    - 1912-1960, undated, (3 folders, 1 volume)
- Writings and Speeches Series, 1909-1984, undated (bulk 1945-1960)
  Chiefly material about Eichelberger's army service. Arranged into subseries: Chronological, Subject, Press Releases, Dictation, and Published Works.
  - Chronological Subseries
    - 1920-1950, (7 folders) (Box 66)
    - 1951-1959, (7 folders) (Box 67)
    - 1960-1961, undated, (3 folders) (Box 68)
  - Subject Subseries
    - Australia, 1948
    - Biak, Schouten Islands; Buna, Hollandia Campaigns; Formation of Eighth Army, 1948 Mar. 18-1949 Feb. 12
    - Buna, New Guinea, 1948
    - Documents regarding the Eighth Army, undated
    - Glider Infantry, 187th, undated
    - Hollandia, New Guinea, 1948
    - Japan, Future of, 1947-1952, undated
    - Japan: (Box 69)
      - Occupation of, 1948-1955, undated
      - War criminals, 1948, undated
    - Korean War, 1953 June 25
    - MacArthur, Douglas, undated
    - Philippines, 1945-1948
    - Siberia, 1946-1947, undated
  - Press Releases Subseries
    - Press Releases, 1938-1984, undated, (4 folders)
  - Dictation Subseries
    This subseries is RESTRICTED. Patrons must sign a waiver form concerning privacy rights before viewing dictation notebooks, index to the typed dictation, and typed dictation transferred from the dictation notebooks found in Boxes 70-74. Contact Research Services.
    - Notebooks of dictation, 1952 Nov. 24-1956 Feb. 6, (3 folders) (Box 70)
    - Notebooks of dictation, 1956 Feb. 6-1959 Jan. 30, (3 folders) (Box 71)
    - Notebooks of dictation, 1959 Jan. 30-1961 Aug., undated, (4 folders) (Box 72)
    - Index of typed dictation, Nos. 1-3 (Box 73)
    - Typed dictation, ca. 1952 Nov.-1961 July, (7 folders)
    - Typed dictation, ca. 1955 July-1961 Sept, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Typed Dictation Victory in Papua, 1954-1959
  - Published Works Subseries
    - Eighth U.S. Army-Up to Now!, 1965 June (Box 75)
    - Engineers of the Southwest Pacific, 1945
    - The Entry of the Soviet Union in to the War Against Japan, 1941-1945
    - History of XI Corps, 1942-1946
    - History of the 3rd Infantry Division in WWII, 1953
    - The Howitzer, 1909 and 1941 (2 volumes) (Box 76)
    - The Howitzer, 1942 (Box 77)
    - Under the Southern Cross, 1949 (Box 78)
    - United States at War, 1945
    - 102nd United States Cavalry, 1941-1942
    - 1909 USMA Eleven Years After, 1920
- Pictures Series, 1872-1984 (bulk 1942-1948).
  Contains photographs chiefly from Eichelberger's army career, including World War II military campaigns, those from the Japanese occupation after World War II, army bases, and ceremonial events, as well as photographs of Eichelberger and his family, including formal portraits and group photographs.The series is subdivided into four subseries: Places and Events, People, Albums, and Miscellaneous.
  Places and events and photographs of people are arranged in alphabetical order, with the exception that those of Eichelberger and his family are arranged before those of others. This series also includes photograph albums, arranged in order by volume number and date, and miscellaneous photographs, arranged in chronological order.
  - Places and Events Subseries
    - Australia, 1942-1943, undated, (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - Figi Islands, 1942-1943
    - Fort Jackson, South Carolina, 1942, undated
    - Fort Leavenworth, Kansas, 1920
    - Japan: Surrender of the Japanese on board the USS Missouri, 1945 Sept. 2
    - Japan: Occupation, 1945-1948, undated, (5 folders) (Box 80)
    - Japan: Occupation, 1945-1949, undated, (5 folders) (Box 81)
    - Japan: Occupation: (Box 82)
      - Hotels, 1946, undated, (2 folders)
      - Kiki and Kyoto Governors Office, undated
      - Visits to:
        - Shrines, 1945-1948, undated
        - Sendai, 1945 Oct. 3
      - Yokohama, 1945-1948, undated
    - New Guinea Campaign, 1942-1945, undated, (5 folders) (Box 83)
    - New Guinea Campaign, 1942-1945, (10 folders) (Box 84)
    - Philippine Campaign, 1942-1945, undated, (6 folders) (Box 85)
    - Philippine Campaign, 1944-1945, undated, (6 folders) (Box 86)
    - Siberia, 1918-1919, undated, (3 folders) (Box 87)
      Siberia photographs have been digitized and are available in Americans in the Land of Lenin - Duke Digital Collections
    - West Point, 1931-1940's, undated, (3 folders)
    - World Tour, 1946, undated (Box 88)
  - People Subseries
    - Eichelberger:
      - Formal Portraits Index
      - Formal portraits, 1940-1949, undated, (4 folders)
    - Eichelberger: (Box 89)
      - Formal portraits, 1940-1949, undated
      - In groups, 1939-1948, undated, (3 folders)
    - Eichelberger: (Box 90)
      - With religious leaders, 1946-1953, undated
      - Ceremonies at retirement, 1947-1949, undated, (2 folders, one phase box)
      - After retirement, 1949-1960, undated
    - Eichelberger: (Box 90a)
      - General and Mrs. Eichelberger at public events, parties, receptions, 1947-1951, undated
      - Eichelberger family, 1872-1956, undated, (2 folders)
      - Unidentified, 1943-1948, undated, (4 folders)
    - Eichelberger: (Box 91)
      - Unidentified, 1943-1948, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1940-1948, undated, (1 folder, 1 phase box)
      - Participants at Eichelberger's induction into the Fort Leavenworth Hall of Fame, 1984
    - A-B (Box 92)
      - (Abbot and Costello, undated; Prince Akihito, 1947 Sept.; Prince Masahito, 1947 Sept.; Barbey, Daniel Edwards (see Northcott, John), undated; Blamey, Thomas Albert, 1943-1953, undated; Brown, Joe E., 1945 April, undated; Byers, Clovis Ethelbert, 1942-1947, undated)
    - Churchill, Winston Leonard Spencer, at Fort Jackson, S.C., 1942 June
    - Co-K